# FERENCZI DÁVID

8124 Káloz Malom 1/B · +36 30 197 4708

ferenczi.david55@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/ferenczi-david



I find myself a precise, responsible, persistant, social and leader type person. In my opinion I learn quickly and I do not have issues with focusing or concentrating. Currently giving it my all to gain solid industrial experience and knowledge. I am thrilled about the opportunities and challenges that allow me to utilize my proficiency with logical thinking and levarage my existing skills. I constantly develop and update my english knowledge. In the future I plan to do an expert level of english language exam. Interested in and open for IT jobs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2020 - 2022

IT SERVICE DESK ANALYST TRAINEE - AGCO HUNGARY KFT.

2022 - 2022

BUSINESS ANALYST TRAINEE - NATIONAL INFOCOMMUNICATIONS SERVICES COMPANY (NISZ ZRT.)

2022 -

IT OPERATIONS ADMINISTRATOR - AGCO HUNGARY KFT.

### **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2022

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - EÖTVÖS LORÁND UNIVERSITY FACULTY OF INFORMATICS

2014 - 2018

TELEKI BLANKA HIGH SCHOOL AND PRIMARY SCHOOL

## **SKILLS**

- MS Office
- Driver license category "B", 2018.
- Frontend Technologies

- Hungarian mother tounge
- English Active, ECL internationally recognized language exam B2 intermediate

#### **HOBBIES**

Physically i am very active, i like to workout a lot, that keeps me in shape and healthy. Keeping my mind active is important as well so reading is part of my life too. My further hobbies are cooking, gardening and practicing self taught projects